ILGWU Legal Department Records 5780/081
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Kellwood (Brownsville). Photocopies of articles in Justice and the Ohio-Kentucky News (Published by ILGWU)., 1972-1976 (Box 25, Folder 5)
  4/72-7/76.
- Kellwood (Brownsville). Photocopies of newspaper articles and notices to company stockholders., 1971-1974 (Box 25, Folder 6)
  10/71-7/74.
- Kellwood (Brownsville). Local newspaper clippings sent by David Freeland to Max Zimny. [folder 1 of 2], 1972-1974 (Box 25, Folder 7)
  10/72- 2/74.
- Kellwood (Brownsville). Local newspaper clippings sent by David Freeland to Max Zimny. [folder 2 of 2], 1972-1974 (Box 25, Folder 8)
- Kellwood (Brownsville). Miscellaneous. (Box 25, Folder 9)
- Landrum-Griffin Law File. Bonding plan., 1960-1963 (Box 25, Folder 10)
  4/60-10/63.
- Landrum-Griffin Law File. Kline vs. Local 55. [folder 1 of 2], 1961-1963 (Box 25, Folder 11)
  11/61-6/63.
- Landrum-Griffin Law File. Kline vs. Local 55. [folder 2 of 2], 1961-1963 (Box 25, Folder 12)
- Landrum-Griffin Law File. Local 415 and Miami Joint Council elections. [folder 1 of 2], 1964-1971 (Box 25, Folder 13)
  2/64-5/71.
- Landrum-Griffin Law File. Local 415 and Miami Joint Council elections. [folder 2 of 2], 1964-1971 (Box 25, Folder 14)
- Landrum-Griffin Law File. File on Fair Plant Properties, Inc.., 1959-1961 (Box 25, Folder 15)
  1/59-2/61.
- Landrum-Griffin Law File. Hilda Perry's complaint about Local 361 election., 1959-1963 (Box 25, Folder 16)
  5/59-6/63.
- Landrum-Griffin Law File. Investigation of Local 73 election., 1971 (Box 25, Folder 17)
  6/71-9/71.
- Landrum-Griffin Law File. Includes references to local by-laws., 1960-1968 (Box 25, Folder 18)
  2/60-1/68.
- Landrum-Griffin Law File. Miscellaneous., 1959-1964 (Box 25, Folder 19)
  7/59-5/64.
- Leonard Workman. General Correspondence. [folder 1 of 4], 1973-1977 (Box 25, Folder 20)
  4/73-11/77. Includes references to arbitration, NLRB cases, union lawsuit and Workman lawsuit.
- Leonard Workman. General Correspondence. [folder 2 of 4], 1973-1977 (Box 25, Folder 21)
- Leonard Workman. General Correspondence. [folder 3 of 4], 1973-1977 (Box 25, Folder 22)
- Leonard Workman. General Correspondence. [folder 4 of 4], 1973-1977 (Box 25, Folder 23)
- Leonard Workman. Arbitration file. Arbitration complaint and decision., 1972-1974 (Box 25, Folder 24)
  12/72-5/74.
- Leonard Workman. Arbitration file. Records for arbitration. (Box 26, Folder 1)
- Leonard Workman. Arbitration file. Proposed stipulation of settlement., 1973 (Box 26, Folder 2)
- Leonard Workman. Arbitration file. Award of July 19, 1973 and confirmation. (Box 26, Folder 3)
  7/73-10/73. Various cases filed by company against union.
- Leonard Workman. NLRB file. [folder 1 of 2], 1972-1973 (Box 26, Folder 4)
  11/72-6/73.
- Leonard Workman. NLRB file. [folder 2 of 2], 1972-1973 (Box 26, Folder 5)
- Leonard Workman. U.S. District Court cases 73 Civ. 1601 and 73 Civ. 2957. [folder 1 of 5], 1973-1974 (Box 26, Folder 6)
  3/73-10/74. Union's attempts to claim arbitration awards.
- Leonard Workman. U.S. District Court cases 73 Civ. 1601 and 73 Civ. 2957. [folder 2 of 5], 1973-1974 (Box 26, Folder 7)
- Leonard Workman. U.S. District Court cases 73 Civ. 1601 and 73 Civ. 2957. [folder 3 of 5], 1973-1974 (Box 26, Folder 8)
- Leonard Workman. U.S. District Court cases 73 Civ. 1601 and 73 Civ. 2957. [folder 41 of 5], 1973-1974 (Box 26, Folder 9)
- Leonard Workman. U.S. District Court cases 73 Civ. 1601 and 73 Civ. 2957. [folder 5 of 5], 1973-1974 (Box 26, Folder 10)
- Leonard Workman. U.S. District Court case 74 Civ. 4883. Correspondence., 1975-1976 (Box 26, Folder 11)
  4/75-8/76. Workman alleges conspiracy by union to bankrupt him.
- Leonard Workman. U.S. District Court case 74 Civ. 4883. Legal documents. [folder 1 of 6], 1974-1977 (Box 26, Folder 12)
  10/74-10/77.
- Leonard Workman. U.S. District Court case 74 Civ. 4883. Legal documents. [folder 2 of 6], 1974-1977 (Box 26, Folder 13)
- Leonard Workman. U.S. District Court case 74 Civ. 4883. Legal documents. [folder 3 of 6], 1974-1977 (Box 26, Folder 14)
- Leonard Workman. U.S. District Court case 74 Civ. 4883. Legal documents. [folder 4 of 6], 1974-1977 (Box 26, Folder 15)
- Leonard Workman. U.S. District Court case 74 Civ. 4883. Legal documents. [folder 5 of 6], 1974-1977 (Box 26, Folder 16)
- Leonard Workman. U.S. District Court case 74 Civ. 4883. Legal documents. [folder 6 of 6], 1974-1977 (Box 26, Folder 17)
- Leonard Workman. Copy of Answer in Budget Dress Corporation case., 1959 (Box 27, Folder 1)
  8/59.
- Leonard Workman. Miscellaneous correspondence., 1973-1974 (Box 27, Folder 2)
  3/73-9/74.
- Level I Sportswear vs. ILGWU., 1980 (Box 27, Folder 3)
- M.H. Yarn vs. Local 57, ILGWU., 1976 (Box 27, Folder 4)
  10/76.
- Murcel Manufacturing Company vs. ILGWU., 1974 (Box 27, Folder 5)
  2/74.
- Okmulgee Mills., 1972-1973 (Box 27, Folder 6)
  2/72-5/73. Involves dispute between Textile Workers Union of America and ILGWU over Oklahoma apparel plant.
- Payne vs. Bobbie Brooks and ILGWU Local 29. General Correspondence., 1974-1976 (Box 27, Folder 7)
  1/74-9/76. Includes Ohio Civil Rights Commission complaints.
- Payne vs. Bobbie Brooks and ILGWU Local 29. General Correspondence., 1977 (Box 27, Folder 8)
  1/77-8/77. Includes determination of Ohio Civil Rights Commission.
- Payne vs. Bobbie Brooks and ILGWU Local 29. General Correspondence., 1977-1978 (Box 27, Folder 9)
  8/77-5/78. Includes U.S. District Court complaint, settlement agreement.
- Payne vs. Bobbie Brooks and ILGWU Local 29. General Correspondence., 1978 (Box 27, Folder 10)
  5/78-11/78. Includes company's motion to dismiss.
- Payne vs. Bobbie Brooks and ILGWU Local 29. Deposition., 1977 (Box 27, Folder 11)
  10/77. Sam Janis.
- Payne vs. Bobbie Brooks and ILGWU Local 29. Depositions., 1977 (Box 27, Folder 12)
  11/77. Mary L. Howard, Wesley Walker, Maggie Terry, Gertrude Jarett, Geraldine Davis, and Theresa Jones.
- Payne vs. Bobbie Brooks and ILGWU Local 29. Depositions., 1977 (Box 27, Folder 13)
  11/77. Eaton Whitehead, Continued Deposition of Mary L. Howard.
- Payne vs. Bobbie Brooks and ILGWU Local 29. Depositions., 1977 (Box 27, Folder 14)
  12/77. Robert T. Rosenfeld.
- Payne vs. Bobbie Brooks and ILGWU Local 29. Depositions., 1978 (Box 27, Folder 15)
  1/78. Wilbur Daniels.
- Payne vs. Bobbie Brooks and ILGWU Local 29. Interview of Wilbur Daniels, Deposition of Margie Payne., 1978 (Box 27, Folder 16)
  1/78.
- Payne vs. Bobbie Brooks and ILGWU Local 29. Summary of testimony on issues, interviews of Carlos Dabila and Emory Murphy., 1978 (Box 27, Folder 17)
  2/78.
- Payne vs. Bobbie Brooks and ILGWU Local 29. Defendant Brooks' First Set of Interrogatories to Plaintiff Hilton., 1977 (Box 27, Folder 18)
  12/77.
- Payne vs. Bobbie Brooks and ILGWU Local 29. Company's employee records. [folder 1 of 4] (Box 27, Folder 19)
- Payne vs. Bobbie Brooks and ILGWU Local 29. Company's employee records. [folder 2 of 4] (Box 27, Folder 20)
- Payne vs. Bobbie Brooks and ILGWU Local 29. Company's employee records. [folder 3 of 4] (Box 27, Folder 21)
- Payne vs. Bobbie Brooks and ILGWU Local 29. Company's employee records. [folder 4 of 4] (Box 27, Folder 22)
- Payne vs. Bobbie Brooks and ILGWU Local 29. Company's employee records. [folder 1 of 4] (Box 28, Folder 1)
- Payne vs. Bobbie Brooks and ILGWU Local 29. Company's employee records. [folder 2 of 4] (Box 28, Folder 2)
- Payne vs. Bobbie Brooks and ILGWU Local 29. Company's employee records. [folder 3 of 4] (Box 28, Folder 3)
- Payne vs. Bobbie Brooks and ILGWU Local 29. Company's employee records. [folder 4 of 4] (Box 28, Folder 4)
- Payne vs. Bobbie Brooks and ILGWU Local 29. Precedents to case. [folder 1 of 2] (Box 28, Folder 5)
- Payne vs. Bobbie Brooks and ILGWU Local 29. Precedents to case. [folder 2 of 2] (Box 28, Folder 6)
- Payne vs. Bobbie Brooks and ILGWU Local 29. Settlement papers., 1978 (Box 28, Folder 7)
  3/78.
- Payne vs. Bobbie Brooks and ILGWU Local 29. Continuation of suit against company., 1980-1981 (Box 28, Folder 8)
  12/80-10/81.
- Payne vs. Bobbie Brooks and ILGWU Local 29. Memoranda about contributions issue., 1980 (Box 28, Folder 9)
  9/80.
- Payne vs. Bobbie Brooks and ILGWU Local 29. Related arbitration., 1979 (Box 28, Folder 10)
  3/79. Grievance of Barbara A. Menefield.
- Putterman vs. Knitgoods Workers' Union, Local 155 ILGWU., 1980-1981 (Box 28, Folder 11)
  2/80-2/81. Alleged discrimination by union.
- Ronner vs. Local 10. General Correspondence. [folder 1 of 2], 1971-1975 (Box 28, Folder 12)
  4/71-8/75.
- Ronner vs. Local 10. General Correspondence. [folder 2 of 2], 1971-1975 (Box 28, Folder 13)
- Ronner vs. Local 10. Deposition of Herman Goldberg., 1972-1973 (Box 28, Folder 14)
  11/72-4/73.
- Ronner vs. Local 10. Deposition of Nat Kline., 1973 (Box 28, Folder 15)
  5/73.
- Ronner vs. Local 10. Deposition of Alfred Ronner. [folder 1 of 3], 1974 (Box 28, Folder 16)
- Ronner vs. Local 10. Deposition of Alfred Ronner. [folder 2 of 3], 1974 (Box 28, Folder 17)
- Ronner vs. Local 10. Deposition of Alfred Ronner. [folder 3 of 3], 1974 (Box 28, Folder 18)
- Ronner vs. Local 10. Materials for Max Zimny's deposition. (Box 28, Folder 19)
- Ronner vs. Local 10. Statements and associated material. [folder 1 of 2], 1972-1974 (Box 29, Folder 1)
  6/72-4/74.
- Ronner vs. Local 10. Statements and associated material. [folder 2 of 2], 1972-1974 (Box 29, Folder 2)
- Ronner vs. Local 10. Settlement agreement file., 1972-1975 (Box 29, Folder 3)
  5/72-10/75.
- Rosario vs. Dolgen, Local 10, and ILGWU. General Correspondence. [folder 1 of 3], 1972-1977 (Box 29, Folder 4)
  8/72-9/77.
- Rosario vs. Dolgen, Local 10, and ILGWU. General Correspondence. [folder 2 of 3], 1972-1977 (Box 29, Folder 5)
- Rosario vs. Dolgen, Local 10, and ILGWU. General Correspondence. [folder 3 of 3], 1972-1977 (Box 29, Folder 6)
- Rosario vs. Dolgen, Local 10, and ILGWU. Minutes of meetings file., 1975 (Box 29, Folder 7)
  1/75-11/75. Includes descriptions of incident in Dolgen's office, minutes of GEB Appeals Committee.
- Rosario vs. Dolgen, Local 10, and ILGWU. Minutes of meetings file., 1975-1976 (Box 29, Folder 8)
  11/75-6/76. Includes agenda of Appeal Committee meeting.
- Rosario vs. Dolgen, Local 10, and ILGWU. Minutes of meetings file., 1975-1978 (Box 29, Folder 9)
  2/75-2/78. Official minutes of Local 10 membership meetings. [Note: Cassette tapes of Trial Committee hearings of 5/21/75, 12/18/75, and 1/8/76, and GEB Appeal Committee hearing on 4/8/76 can be found in Box 45, file folder 19.]
- Rosario vs. Dolgen, Local 10 and ILGWU. U.S. District Court case., 1975-1978 (Box 29, Folder 10)
  12/75-4/78. Affidavits of Tomas Rosario.
- Rosario vs. Dolgen, Local 10 and ILGWU. U.S. District Court case., 1978 (Box 29, Folder 10a)
  2/13/78. 1 bound volume. Deposition of Tomas Rosario.
- Rosario vs. Dolgen, Local 10 and ILGWU. U.S. District Court case., 1978 (Box 29, Folder 10b)
  2/14/78. 1 bound volume. Continued Deposition of Tomas Rosario.
- Rosario vs. Dolgen, Local 10 and ILGWU. U.S. District Court case., 1978 (Box 29, Folder 10c)
  2/23/78. 1 bound volume. Continued Deposition of Tomas Rosario.
- Rosario vs. Dolgen, Local 10 and ILGWU. U.S. District Court case., 1978 (Box 29, Folder 10d)
  3/8/78. 1 bound volume. Deposition of Tomas Rosario.
- Rosario vs. Dolgen, Local 10 and ILGWU. U.S. District Court case., 1978 (Box 29, Folder 10e)
  2/15/78. 1 bound volume. Deposition of Ovidio Vega.
- Rosario vs. Dolgen, Local 10 and ILGWU. U.S. District Court case., 1978 (Box 29, Folder 10f)
  2/27/78. 1 bound volume. Examination Before Trial of Ovidio Vega.
- Rosario vs. Dolgen, Local 10 and ILGWU. U.S. District Court case., 1978 (Box 29, Folder 10g)
  2/21/78. 1 bound volume. Deposition of Raymond E. Cabel.
- Rosario vs. Dolgen, Local 10 and ILGWU. U.S. District Court case., 1978 (Box 29, Folder 10h)
  2/27/78. 1 bound volume. Examination Before Trial of Raymond E. Cabel.
- Rosario vs. Dolgen, Local 10 and ILGWU. U.S. District Court case., 1978 (Box 29, Folder 11)
  3/78. Examinations Before Trial of Beraldine Acha, Phillip Calderalla, and Vincent A. Lanzante (police officers).
- Rosario vs. Dolgen, Local 10 and ILGWU. U.S. District Court case. Evidence file., 1971-1978 (Box 29, Folder 12)
  2/71-2/78. Impartial chairman's decisions on cut-up shops.
- Rosario vs. Dolgen, Local 10 and ILGWU. U.S. District Court case. Evidence file., 1971-1977 (Box 29, Folder 13)
  Ballots from Local 10 elections of 1971, 1974, and 1977.
- Rosario vs. Dolgen, Local 10 and ILGWU. U.S. District Court case. Evidence file., 1976 (Box 29, Folder 14)
  8/76-9/76. Galaxy Costume Corporation.
- Rosario vs. Dolgen, Local 10 and ILGWU. U.S. District Court case. Evidence file. (Box 29, Folder 15)
  Local 10 handbook and ILGWU constitution.
- Rosario vs. Dolgen, Local 10 and ILGWU. U.S. District Court case. Evidence file., 1975 (Box 29, Folder 16)
  Wages of Rosario, Vega, and Cabel for 1975.
- Rosario vs. Dolgen, Local 10 and ILGWU. U.S. District Court case. [folder 1 of 2] (Box 29, Folder 17)
  Plaintiff's exhibits.
- Rosario vs. Dolgen, Local 10 and ILGWU. U.S. District Court case. [folder 2 of 2] (Box 29, Folder 18)
- Rosario vs. Dolgen, Local 10 and ILGWU. U.S. District Court case. (Box 30, Folder 1)
  Plaintiff's exhibits continued.
- Rosario vs. Dolgen, Local 10 and ILGWU. U.S. District Court case. (Box 30, Folder 2)
  Defendant Dolgen's exhibits.
- Rosario vs. Dolgen, Local 10 and ILGWU. U.S. District Court case. [folder 1 of 3] (Box 30, Folder 3)
  Defendant Local 10's exhibits.
- Rosario vs. Dolgen, Local 10 and ILGWU. U.S. District Court case. [folder 2 of 3] (Box 30, Folder 4)
- Rosario vs. Dolgen, Local 10 and ILGWU. U.S. District Court case. [folder 3 of 3] (Box 30, Folder 5)
- Rosario vs. Dolgen, Local 10 and ILGWU. U.S. District Court case. (Box 30, Folder 6)
  Defendant ILGWU's exhibits.
- Rosario vs. Dolgen, Local 10 and ILGWU. U.S. District Court case. (Box 30, Folder 7)
  Exhibit-related materials.
- Rosario vs. Dolgen, Local 10 and ILGWU. U.S. District Court case. Court documents., 1975 (Box 30, Folder 8)
  9/75-12/75. Includes Complaint of plaintiffs, Notice of Motion to Dismiss.
- Rosario vs. Dolgen, Local 10 and ILGWU. U.S. District Court case. Court documents., 1975 (Box 30, Folder 9)
  12/75. Includes Reply Affidavit of Nat Klein.
- Rosario vs. Dolgen, Local 10 and ILGWU. U.S. District Court case. Court documents., 1975-1976 (Box 30, Folder 10)
  12/75-8/76. Includes Answers of defendants.
- Rosario vs. Dolgen, Local 10 and ILGWU. U.S. District Court case. Court documents., 1976 (Box 30, Folder 11)
  8/76. Includes Notice of Motion [for Summary Judgment].
- Rosario vs. Dolgen, Local 10 and ILGWU. U.S. District Court case. Court documents., 1976 (Box 30, Folder 12)
- Rosario vs. Dolgen, Local 10 and ILGWU. U.S. District Court case. Court documents., 1976 (Box 30, Folder 13)
  8/76-9/76. Includes Affidavit of Sol. C. Chaikin.
- Rosario vs. Dolgen, Local 10 and ILGWU. U.S. District Court case. Court documents., 1976-1977 (Box 30, Folder 14)
  9/76-5/77. Includes [Max Zimny's] Affidavit in Opposition to Plaintiffs' Motion for a Preliminary Injunction.
- Rosario vs. Dolgen, Local 10 and ILGWU. U.S. District Court case. Court documents., 1977-1978 (Box 30, Folder 15)
  8/77-2/78. Includes Memorandum in Opposition to Plaintiffs' Motion for a Preliminary Injunction.
- Rosario vs. Dolgen, Local 10 and ILGWU. U.S. District Court case. Court documents., 1978 (Box 30, Folder 16)
  3/78-4/78. Includes Trial Memorandum of Amalgamated Ladies' Garment Cutters' Union, Local 10.
- Rosario vs. Dolgen, Local 10 and ILGWU. U.S. District Court case., 1976-1978 (Box 30, Folder 17)
  7/76-3/78. Docket entries.
- Rosario vs. Dolgen, Local 10 and ILGWU. U.S. District Court case., 1977-1978 (Box 30, Folder 18)
  1/77-2/78. Demands, requests, and notices for the takings and productions of documents.
- Rosario vs. Dolgen, Local 10 and ILGWU. U.S. District Court case., 1978 (Box 30, Folder 19)
  2/78-4/78. Jury-related documents.
- Rosario vs. Dolgen, Local 10 and ILGWU. U.S. District Court case., 1978 (Box 30, Folder 20)
  4/78. Voir dire questions.
- Rosario vs. Dolgen, Local 10 and ILGWU. U.S. District Court case. Transcript., 1976 (Box 31, Folder 1)
  Transcripts of hearings on 9/8/76 and 9/14/76.
- Rosario vs. Dolgen, Local 10 and ILGWU. U.S. District Court case. Transcript., 1976-1977 (Box 31, Folder 2)
  Transcripts of hearings on 9/17/76 and 5/13/77.
- Rosario vs. Dolgen, Local 10 and ILGWU. U.S. District Court case. Transcript., 1978 (Box 31, Folder 3)
  Transcripts of trial on 4/4/78 and 4/5/78.
- Rosario vs. Dolgen, Local 10 and ILGWU. U.S. District Court case. Transcript., 1978 (Box 31, Folder 4)
  Transcript of trial on 4/6/78.
- Rosario vs. Dolgen, Local 10 and ILGWU. U.S. District Court case. Transcript. [folder 1 of 2], 1978 (Box 31, Folder 5)
  Transcript of trial on 4/10/78.
- Rosario vs. Dolgen, Local 10 and ILGWU. U.S. District Court case. Transcript. [folder 2 of 2], 1978 (Box 31, Folder 6)
- Rosario vs. Dolgen, Local 10 and ILGWU. U.S. District Court case. Transcript., 1978 (Box 31, Folder 7)
  Transcript of trial on 4/11/78.
- Rosario vs. Dolgen, Local 10 and ILGWU. U.S. District Court case. Transcript., 1978 (Box 31, Folder 8)
  Transcript of trial on 4/12/78.
- Rosario vs. Dolgen, Local 10 and ILGWU. U.S. District Court case. Transcript. [folder 1 of 2], 1978 (Box 31, Folder 9)
  Transcript of trial on 4/13/78.
- Rosario vs. Dolgen, Local 10 and ILGWU. U.S. District Court case. Transcript. [folder 2 of 2], 1978 (Box 31, Folder 10)
- Rosario vs. Dolgen, Local 10 and ILGWU. U.S. District Court case. Transcript., 1978 (Box 31, Folder 11)
  Transcript of trial on 4/17/78.
- Rosario vs. Dolgen, Local 10 and ILGWU. U.S. District Court case. Transcript., 1978 (Box 31, Folder 12)
  Transcript of trial on 4/18/78.
- Rosario vs. Dolgen, Local 10 and ILGWU. U.S. District Court case. Transcript., 1978 (Box 31, Folder 13)
  Transcript of trial on 4/19/78.
- Rosario vs. Dolgen, Local 10 and ILGWU. U.S. District Court case. Transcript., 1978 (Box 31, Folder 14)
  Transcript of trial on 4/20/78.
- Rosario vs. Dolgen, Local 10 and ILGWU. U.S. District Court case. Transcript. [folder 1 of 2], 1978 (Box 31, Folder 15)
  Transcript of trial on 4/24/78.
- Rosario vs. Dolgen, Local 10 and ILGWU. U.S. District Court case. Transcript. [folder 2 of 2], 1978 (Box 31, Folder 16)
- Rosario vs. Dolgen, Local 10 and ILGWU. U.S. District Court case. Transcript. [folder 1 of 2], 1978 (Box 31, Folder 17)
  Transcript of trial on 4/25/78.
- Rosario vs. Dolgen, Local 10 and ILGWU. U.S. District Court case. Transcript. [folder 2 of 2], 1978 (Box 31, Folder 18)
- Rosario vs. Dolgen, Local 10 and ILGWU. U.S. District Court case. Transcript., 1978 (Box 32, Folder 1)
  Transcript of trial on 4/26/78.
- Rosario vs. Dolgen, Local 10 and ILGWU. U.S. District Court case., 1978-1979 (Box 32, Folder 2)
  5/78-9/79. Reimbursement agreement file between Abe Dolgen and Local 10.
- Rosario vs. Dolgen, Local 10 and ILGWU. U.S. Court of Appeals case. [folder 1 of 6] (Box 32, Folder 3)
  Defendants' exhibits.
- Rosario vs. Dolgen, Local 10 and ILGWU. U.S. Court of Appeals case. [folder 2 of 6] (Box 32, Folder 4)
- Rosario vs. Dolgen, Local 10 and ILGWU. U.S. Court of Appeals case. [folder 3 of 6] (Box 32, Folder 5)
- Rosario vs. Dolgen, Local 10 and ILGWU. U.S. Court of Appeals case. [folder 4 of 6] (Box 32, Folder 6)
- Rosario vs. Dolgen, Local 10 and ILGWU. U.S. Court of Appeals case. [folder 5 of 6] (Box 32, Folder 7)
- Rosario vs. Dolgen, Local 10 and ILGWU. U.S. Court of Appeals case. [folder 61 of 6] (Box 32, Folder 8)
- Rosario vs. Dolgen, Local 10 and ILGWU. U.S. Court of Appeals case. (Box 32, Folder 9)
  Max Zimny's working papers.
- Rosario vs. Dolgen, Local 10 and ILGWU. U.S. Court of Appeals case 76-7472. [folder 1 of 3], 1976-1977 (Box 32, Folder 10)
  9/76-1/77. Court documents.
- Rosario vs. Dolgen, Local 10 and ILGWU. U.S. Court of Appeals case 76-7472. [folder 2 of 3], 1976-1977 (Box 32, Folder 11)
- Rosario vs. Dolgen, Local 10 and ILGWU. U.S. Court of Appeals case 76-7472. [folder 3 of 3], 1976-1977 (Box 32, Folder 12)
- Rosario vs. Dolgen, Local 10 and ILGWU. U.S. Court of Appeals case 76-7472. (Box 32, Folder 12a)
  Joint Appendix volumes I and II. 2 bound volumes.
- Rosario vs. Dolgen, Local 10 and ILGWU. U.S. Court of Appeals case 78-7335-37., 1978 (Box 32, Folder 13)
  9/78. Court documents.
- Rosario vs. Dolgen, Local 10 and ILGWU. U.S. Court of Appeals case 78-7335-37. (Box 32, Folder 13a)
- Rosario vs. Dolgen, Local 10, and ILGWU. Court costs., 1976-1979 (Box 33, Folder 1)
  12/76-1/79.
- Rosario vs. Dolgen, Local 10, and ILGWU. Miscellaneous. (Box 33, Folder 2)
- Sarner vs. Sigman, et al.., 1924 (Box 33, Folder 3)
  11/24.
- Slate Belt. Mickus. General Correspondence., 1957-1958 (Box 33, Folder 4)
  3/57-1/58.
- Slate Belt. Mickus. General Correspondence., 1958 (Box 33, Folder 5)
  2/58-4/58.
- Slate Belt. Mickus. General Correspondence., 1958 (Box 33, Folder 6)
  5/58-11/58.
- Slate Belt. Mickus. General Correspondence., 1959 (Box 33, Folder 7)
  1/59-3/59.
- Slate Belt. Mickus. General Correspondence., 1959 (Box 33, Folder 8)
  3/59-4/59.
- Slate Belt. Mickus. General Correspondence., 1959 (Box 33, Folder 9)
  4/59.
- Slate Belt. Mickus. General Correspondence., 1959 (Box 33, Folder 10)
  4/59-8/59.
- Slate Belt. Mickus. General Correspondence., 1959-1960 (Box 33, Folder 11)
  8/59-12/60.
- Slate Belt. Mickus. Newspaper clippings., 1959-1960 (Box 33, Folder 12)
  3/59-2/60.
- Spitzer vs. Local 10. General Correspondence., 1979 (Box 33, Folder 13)
  5/79-9/79.
- Spitzer vs. Local 10. Minutes of meetings between David Spitzer and Israel Mechlowicz., 1979 (Box 33, Folder 14)
  4/79-10/79.
- Spitzer vs. Local 10. Evidence file., 1941 (Box 33, Folder 15)
  Local 10 1941 constitution.
- Spitzer vs. Local 10. Evidence file. (Box 33, Folder 16)
  Documents and vouchers copied for Spitzer.
- Spitzer vs. Local 10. Evidence file. (Box 33, Folder 17)
  General Executive Board approval of salary increases.
- Spitzer vs. Local 10. Precedents and statutes. (Box 33, Folder 18)
- Spitzer vs. Local 10. Transcript of GEB Appeal Committee hearing., 1979 (Box 33, Folder 18a)
  10/11/79. 1 bound volume.
- Spitzer vs. Local 10. Exhibits for GEB Appeal Committee hearing. [folder 1 of 3], 1979 (Box 33, Folder 19)
  10/11/79.
- Spitzer vs. Local 10. Exhibits for GEB Appeal Committee hearing. [folder 2 of 3], 1979 (Box 33, Folder 20)
- Spitzer vs. Local 10. Exhibits for GEB Appeal Committee hearing. [folder 3 of 3], 1979 (Box 33, Folder 21)
- Spitzer vs. Local 10. Exhibits for GEB Appeal Committee hearing., 1979 (Box 34, Folder 1)
  10/29/79.
- Spitzer vs. Local 10. Transcript of GEB Appeal Committee hearing., 1979 (Box 34, Folder 1a)
  10/29/79. 1 bound volume.
- Spitzer vs. Local 10. Transcript of GEB Appeal Committee hearing., 1979 (Box 34, Folder 1b)
  10/31/79. 1 bound volume.
- Spitzer vs. Local 10. Exhibits for GEB Appeal Committee hearing., 1979 (Box 34, Folder 2)
  10/31/79.
- Spitzer vs. Local 10. Transcript of 1980 Convention Appeal Committee hearing and related materials. (Box 34, Folder 3)
  9/27/80.
- Spitzer vs. Local 10. GEB Appeal Committee file on an earlier case., 1975-1976 (Box 34, Folder 4)
  10/75-10/76.
- Spitzer vs. Local 10. NLRB case 2-CB-7842., 1979 (Box 34, Folder 5)
  5/79-7/79.
- Spitzer vs. Local 10. Other cases involving reimbursement., 1977-1979 (Box 34, Folder 6)
  10/77-7/79.
- United States of America vs. Interstate Dress Carriers. Minutes of trial. [folder 1 of 2], 1980 (Box 34, Folder 7)
  4/22/80 and 4/23/80.
- United States of America vs. Interstate Dress Carriers. Minutes of trial. [folder 2 of 2], 1980 (Box 34, Folder 8)
- United States of America vs. Interstate Dress Carriers. Minutes of trial., 1980 (Box 34, Folder 8a)
  4/24/80. 1 bound volume.